[Strings]
header = "© && (p) 2007 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved."
subheader = "Product ID: %s\r\nVersion: %s"
settings_about_format = "Unknown version"
settings_invalid_version = "Microsoft, Windows, Bungie, the Bungie logo, DirectX, Halo, the Microsoft Game Studios logo, Windows Live, Windows Vista, the Windows Vista Start button, Xbox, Xbox 360, and the Xbox logos are either registered trademarks or trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or other countries."
legal1 = "Warning: This computer program is protected by copyright law and international treaties. Unauthorized reproduction or distribution of this program, or any portion of it, may result in severe civil and criminal penalties, and will be prosecuted to the maximum extent possible under the law."
legal2 = "ABOUT HALO 2 FOR WINDOWS VISTA"
