[Strings]
header = "Specify what type of game you are looking for and join a game from the browser."
search_help = "Browse Games"
find_games = "Custom Match"
optimatch = "Quickmatch"
quickmatch = "Create a party, invite your Friends, and play a custom game or find games together."
arranged_game = "Look for a game of Halo 2 in the browser."
browse_help = "Jump right into a matchmade game of Halo 2 on Live."
quickmatch_help = "Jump right into a matchmade game of Halo 2 on Live."
