[Strings]
x06_0010_soc = "A Hierarch is dead, Commander. "
x06_0020_pot = "His murderer was within our grasp! If you had not withdrawn our Phantoms -"
x06_0030_soc = "Are you questioning my decision\?"
x06_0040_pot = "No, Holy One. I only wish to express my concern that the Brutes - "
x06_0050_soc = "Recommissioning the guard was a radical step. But recent events have made it abundantly clear that the Elites can no longer guarantee our safety."
x06_0060_pot = "I shall relay your decision to the Council. "
x06_0070_soc = "Politics. How tiresome."
x06_0080_pot = "Do you know, Arbiter, the Elites have threatened to resign\?  "
x06_0090_pot = "To quit the High Council\? Because of this...exchange of hats\?"
x06_0100_pot = "We have always been your protectors."
x06_0110_der = "These are trying times - for all of us. "
x06_0120_pot = "Even as the humans' annihilation filled us with satisfaction, the loss of one of the Sacred Rings wracked our hearts with grief!"
x06_0130_pom = "Putting aside our sorrow, we renewed our faith in the prophecy that other rings would be found."
x06_0140_pot = "And see how our faith has been rewarded!"
x06_0150_pot = "Halo...its divine wind will rush through the stars, propelling all who are worthy along the path to salvation! "
x06_0160_pom = "But how to start this process\? For ages we searched for one who might unlock the secrets of the rings - an Oracle."
x06_0170_pot = "And with your help, we found it!"
x06_0180_pot = "With appropriate humility we plied the Oracle with questions, and it, with clarity and grace, has shown us the key!"
x06_0190_pom = "You will journey to the surface of the ring, and retrieve this Sacred Icon."
x06_0200_pot = "With it, we shall fulfill our promise - "
x06_0210_pot = "Salvation for all!"
x06_0220_pom = "And begin the Great Journey!"
x06_0230_pot = "Once the shield is down..."
c06_1010_tar = "we will head straight to the Library."
c06_1020_tar = "I do not wish to keep the Hierarchs waiting. "
c06_1030_tar = "The human that killed the Prophet of Regret...who was it\?"
c06_1040_der = "Who do you think\?"
c06_1050_tar = "The Demon is here\?"
c06_1060_der = "(affirmative grunt) "
c06_1070_tar = "Why\?"
c06_1080_tar = "Looking for a little payback\?"
c06_1090_tar = "Retrieving the Icon is my only concern."
c06_1100_der = "(laugh) Of course."
c06_1110_tar = "An Enforcer! Draw it off!"
c06_1111_tar = "Lower the shield, Arbiter!"
c06_1120_tar = "I'll pick you up when you've finished!"
c06_1130_tar = "This is unprecedented. Unacceptable."
