[Strings]
header = "New Campaign"
solo = "Resume"
resume_solo_campaign = "Select Level"
restart_solo_campaign = "Cooperative"
coop = "Cooperative"
restart_coop_campaign = "Resume - Load your most recent saved checkpoint.\r\nSelect Level - Select an unlocked level. Warning, you will lose saved progress from your current level.\r\nCooperative - Play a 2-player cooperative campaign split screen."
campaign_help = "Start a new campaign."
solo_help = "Load your most recent saved checkpoint."
resume_solo_help = "Select an unlocked level. Warning, you will lose saved progress for your current level."
restart_solo_help = "Play a cooperative campaign split screen with another player."
coop_help = "Resume Achievements Checkpoint"
resume_achievements = "Load your most recent checkpoint from Live and continue your quest for Achievements"
resume_achievements_help = "Load your most recent checkpoint from Live and continue your quest for Achievements"
