[Strings]
variant_select_screen_header = "SELECT VARIANT"
slayer = "Slayer"
king_of_the_hill = "King of the Hill"
oddball = "Oddball"
juggernaut = "Juggernaut"
capture_the_flag = "Capture the Flag"
assault = "Assault"
territories = "Territories"
slayer_description_text = "Kill as many of your opponents as you can. The player with the most points wins."
king_of_the_hill_description_text = "Gain control of the hill to earn time. Keep your opponents off and earn the most time to win."
oddball_description_text = "Find the ball and hold on to it to earn time. The player with the most time wins."
juggernaut_description_text = "Work together to take down the Juggernaut. Beware, you kill the Juggernaut, you become the Juggernaut, and only the Juggernaut can win."
capture_the_flag_description_text = "Invade your opponent’s stronghold, heist their flag, and bring it back to your base to score."
assault_description_text = "Carry your bomb into the enemy base and arm it. Once armed, drop it on the enemy bomb post to score."
territories_description_text = "Find and control territories on the map. The more territories you control, the faster you earn time."
slayer_uppercase = "SLAYER"
king_of_the_hill_uppercase = "KING OF THE HILL"
oddball_uppercase = "ODDBALL"
juggernaut_uppercase = "JUGGERNAUT"
capture_the_flag_uppercase = "CAPTURE THE FLAG"
assault_uppercase = "ASSAULT"
territories_uppercase = "TERRITORIES"
create_new_variant = "Create New..."
built_in_variant = "Built-in Variant (cannot edit)"
create_new_description_text = "Select this option if you would like to create a new variant. Select a built-in variant to customize your own version of it."
mp_map_key = "&a-button SELECT  &b-button BACK"
built_in_variant_lobby = "Built-in Variant"
none = "This is a custom, player-created variant."
0 = "Prepare for a classic Slayer duel to the death. 25 points to win."
1 = "Take on a small team of enemies in a straight up Slayer throw down. 50 points to win."
2 = "Get ready for an explosive game of Rockets. All rocket launchers, no motion sensor. 25 points to win."
3 = "Steady your shot and aim high. All weapons are sniper rifles and there's no motion sensor. 15 points wins."
4 = "Sharpen your Energy Sword and power up your overshields. 25 points wins this game."
5 = "Everyone has active camo, so watch your back. 15 points wins this game."
6 = "Everyone has active camo and you can organize into up to 8 teams. First team to 25 points wins."
7 = "You have just one life per round. The last player standing wins a round. First to win 3 rounds wins the game."
8 = "You have just one life and everyone is invisible. Last player standing wins a round. First to win 3 rounds takes the cake."
9 = "Get ready for a classic game of free-for-all Oddball. Hold the ball for 2 minutes to win."
10 = "This game of Oddball with nothing but rocket launchers is a real blast. Control the ball for 1 minute to win."
11 = "Up to 8 teams can go head to head in this game of team Oddball. First team with 2 minutes ball control wins."
12 = "Team Oddball with a twist. Everyone on your team must hold the ball for at least 30 seconds to win."
13 = "Stay on the hill for a total of 2 minutes to win the game. Hill does not move."
14 = "Your team must take the hill and control it uncontested for 1 minute to win. Hill does not move."
15 = "Control the hill uncontested to earn time. Everyone has active camo and the hill does not move. 1 minute wins."
16 = "The hill moves once a minute. Be the first to earn 2 minutes on it to take the crown."
17 = "Your team must earn just 1 minute uncontested on the moving hill to take the crown."
18 = "One player is the Juggernaut, the other 2 are teammates. Only the Juggernaut can score and 10 points wins the game."
19 = "The Juggernaut has active camo and a motion sensor. You don't, so work together to corner him and take him out. 10 points wins."
20 = "The Dreadnaut is an unstoppable beast. Fear him but work together to take him out. 20 kills as Juggernaut wins the game."
21 = "Defend your flag while launching a coordinated attack on your enemy's flag. 3 captures to win."
22 = "Defend your flag while capturing the enemy's. 3 points wins, flag must be home to score, flag may be returned."
23 = "Take turns on offense/defense. A capture wins a round. Flag may not be returned. Rounds last 3 minutes. First to 3 wins."
24 = "Intense 2 minute rounds of alternating offense/defense. A capture wins a round. Flag may not be returned. First to 3 wins."
25 = "Defend your base while trying to deliver your bomb into the enemy's base. 3 successful bombings wins."
26 = "Take turns on offense/defense. A successful bombing wins a round. First to 3 wins. No bomb return. Rounds last 3 minutes."
27 = "Intense 2 minute rounds of offense/defense. A successful bombing wins a round. Bomb may not be returned. First to 3 wins."
28 = "There's just one bomb that starts in the middle. Use it to bomb the enemy base 3 times to win."
29 = "There are just 3 territories. Earn 3 minutes control time before your opponents by owning a majority of them."
30 = "Own a majority of territories to earn 5 minutes control time before your opponents."
31 = "There's just one territory on the map. Work with your team to control it for 2 minutes to win."
32 = "Grab your pistol and load your shotgun! 2 minutes wins a round. Rounds last 3 minutes. First to 3 rounds wins."
33 = "One player is the Juggernaut while 3 others are teammates. Earn 10 points as the Juggernaut to win the game."
34 = "An odd game of ball with random weapons. Earn 2 minutes ball control time to win."
35 = "You have just 1 life and no motion sensor in this single bomb game. 10 second arming, 3 minute rounds, first to 3 wins."
36 = "You're invisible but you have no motion sensor. You're being hunted, so watch out! 3 rounds wins, 5 points wins a round."
37 = "Bring out the big guns to fight for control of just 2 territories. Everyone has overshields, 5 minutes control time wins."
38 = "Tense rounds with swords and no motion sensor. Own the ball for 30 seconds to win a round. First to 3 wins."
race = "Race"
headhunter = "Headhunter"
vip = "VIP"
medic = "Medic"
infection = "Infection"
race_description_text = "The first player to complete several laps by touching all the flag points wins the race."
headhunter_description_text = "Collect the heads of the fallen. The more you save, the more points you score bringing them to your home base."
vip_description_text = "One player on each team is Very Important. Take down the enemy's VIP for points, but take care of your own."
medic_description_text = "Each team has a medic. As long as your medic is alive, you respawn when killed.  The objective is to kill the other teams."
infection_description_text = "The timeless struggle of human versus zombie. If you die by a zombie's hand, you join their ranks."
race_uppercase = "RACE"
headhunter_uppercase = "HEADHUNTER"
vip_uppercase = "VIP"
medic_uppercase = "MEDIC"
infection_uppercase = "INFECTION"
39 = "The first player to complete several laps by touching all the flag points wins the race."
40 = "Collect skulls and bring them back to base to score. Just like in real life."
41 = "Take down the enemy VIP while defending your own."
42 = "Eliminate the enemy medic to permanently eliminate the enemy team."
43 = "Some players start off as zombies and seek to devour humans."
